<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><updated>2018-10-08T12:50:25+00:00</updated><icon>https://www.redditstatic.com/icon.png/</icon><id>/r/tifu/.rss</id><link rel="self" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/.rss" type="application/atom+xml" /><link rel="alternate" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/" type="text/html" /><logo>https://a.thumbs.redditmedia.com/dJbIoj1O3ZfaBtYWtsCk1FRtbxdLQvlbP0WngEy85y0.png</logo><subtitle>WELCOME TO /r/TIFU! Today I Fucked Up is a community for the dumbass in all of us. We all have those moments where we do something ridiculously stupid. Let us make each other feel better about ourselves. Come and check it out! Why you should join us: It's funny, interesting, cringe-worthy, laugh-causing, smile-inducing, feel-good, ridiculous, humor, humorous, humerus, stupid, cool, awesome, but mostly because it's the best community on reddit.</subtitle><title>Today I Fucked Up</title><entry><author><name>/u/AutoModerator</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to the common fuck-ups megathread.&lt;/strong&gt; You &lt;a href=&quot;https://redd.it/4ifanz&quot;&gt;suggested it&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://redd.it/4ir8p4&quot;&gt;we listened&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You may be wondering what a &amp;quot;common fuck-up&amp;quot; is. Normally they are topics that are non-noteworthy or unoriginal, the minor things we fuck up. You can view them in our &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/commonfuckups&quot;&gt;[wiki]&lt;/a&gt;. While we are being lax on this rule within this thread, we want to remind everyone that every other rule still applies, which can be found on our sidebar or &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/w/rules&quot;&gt;[wiki/rules]&lt;/a&gt; page. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We will be having 2 megathreads a week:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Monday-Friday for normal common fuck-ups&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Friday-Sunday for nfsw (rule 4) common fuck-ups&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;wiki pages: / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/rules&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;detailed rules page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/about/sidebar&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;sidebar link&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/commonfuckups&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;list of common fuck-ups&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/flairs&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;flair/NFSW filters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/about/rules&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;rules(report reasons)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/index&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;FUOTW archive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;/r/tifu/wiki/subs&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;other subs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; /&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator&quot;&gt; /u/AutoModerator &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdjwy/common_fuckups_megathread_october_08_2018/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdjwy/common_fuckups_megathread_october_08_2018/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mdjwy</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdjwy/common_fuckups_megathread_october_08_2018/" /><updated>2018-10-08T10:02:07+00:00</updated><title>Common Fuck-Ups Megathread - October 08, 2018</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Shylo132</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Shylo132</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello TIFU Community!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We have made a few changes to the rules so please be sure to review the the sidebar!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;h6&gt;Changes&lt;/h6&gt; &lt;p&gt;A few items from our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/wiki/commonfuckups&quot;&gt;common fuckups&lt;/a&gt; list have been moved to Rule 8 section D and E.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;h6&gt;FROM THE WIKI:&lt;/h6&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;h3&gt;8d. Posts dealing with shit/piss (including but not limited to: on yourself or others)&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;In a world of 7 billion people we all do this and it is very common so if you wish to paint a shit picture you better learn how to write well enough to do it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;8e. Touching yourself (ie. genitals, eyes, etc.) after touching something unpleasant without washing/putting something unpleasant on your genitals.&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;This includes but is not limited too Icy Hot or jalapenos and anything else that can burn, irritate or cause reason to think it is a fuck up.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;~~&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/wiki/rules&quot;&gt;Wiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;h6&gt;Fun Fact:&lt;/h6&gt; &lt;p&gt;A large portion of the Pumpkin Spice market comes from the alcohol industry including pumpkin wines, pumpkin spirits, pumpkin moonshine and pumpkin beers making up nearly 20% of the craft beer market.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please note that these types of posts will no longer be tolerated so please leave them out when creating or retelling your stories! Time to bring out your creative writing and literary skills to portray the picture you want us to see.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sup&gt;--Shylo132&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Shylo132&quot;&gt; /u/Shylo132 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9gpbpu/rule_updates/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9gpbpu/rule_updates/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9gpbpu</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9gpbpu/rule_updates/" /><updated>2018-09-17T23:10:30+00:00</updated><title>Rule updates</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/blazer2345</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/blazer2345</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened a few years ago when I was 19.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I went on vacation with my family over the holidays, so we were out of town for Christmas. We were gone for ten days and I never got the chance to jerk off on the trip. We got back home late (around one in the morning) so we all just brought out stuff in and immediately went to bed. The next morning, everyone goes out to breakfast but I stayed home to sleep some more... is what I said. I actually wanted to stay home because I woke up with a massive hard on and I wanted a good amount of time to masturbate without being bothered.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m about 15-20 minutes in when my Mom calls me. I take my hand off my dick and answer the phone. I can&amp;#39;t be touching myself while talking to her lol. She tells me that Allison (family friend, her and my mom go way back) is going to be stopping at the house to drop off some late Christmas gifts for us, so I have to answer the door/let her in, etc. I tell her all right and figure I have time to finish before I have to do this. Well I&amp;#39;m just about to climax when the doorbell rings. Ah shit. Guess I&amp;#39;ll take care of this then finish myself off after.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I quickly put on a pair of sweatpants, pull the &amp;#39;ol flip and tuck and put on a shirt. I answered the door and she immediately comes in and gives me a hug. Now, the shirt I was wearing was a little bit tight so it wasn&amp;#39;t the best fit. When I reached out to hug her that pulled the shirt up a little bit, exposing the head of my erect (and very sensitive) penis.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, there are a couple of things that came in to play: She was wearing an extremely soft cashmere sweater. She hugged me very tightly and began to rock back and forth a little bit, as we hadn&amp;#39;t seen each other in a very long time and she&amp;#39;s a close family friend. So after a few seconds of this I feel my cock starting to twitch and I realized she set my virgin dick over the edge. My brain begins to cloud as the orgasm quickly builds but I&amp;#39;m trying to do anything to get out of this... I pulled away from the hug just as I started cumming but it was too late. Keep in mind I hadn&amp;#39;t had came in ten days so this was a huge &amp;#39;gasm.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I grunted an apology as my dick sprayed her and myself with man chowder. She was extremely taken aback but she just went to the bathroom and tried to clean it off as best she could. I apologized profusely and told her i wasn&amp;#39;t sure what happened. She said it was fine. The real fuck up was that a week later she called me and told me that I had to buy her a new sweater because it was a gift from her husband and she didn&amp;#39;t want to explain what happened. Plus, you can&amp;#39;t get cum out of cashmere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;tl;dr Family friend hugged me while my dick was extremely sensitive and it set me over the edge. Came all over her and myself. She made me replace her sweater which cost over $200.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;EDIT: I did not expect this story to blow up so much, wow. Thanks, it&amp;#39;s been hilarious reading your comments!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;EDIT 2: Thank you to the kind person who gilded my post! My first ever Reddit gold is for cumming on my mom&amp;#39;s friend, not sure how I feel about that...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;EDIT 3: Just to clear a few things up:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did not do this intentionally, it was circumstantial. I also didn&amp;#39;t just stand there and empty my clip on her. She only caught the first couple ropes and then got out of the line of fire as I was getting it back in my pants, where I finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;#39;t have time to put on boxers, and sweatpants just made more sense so my only option was to tuck. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did not keep the original sweater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;For being 50 and a friend of my mom&amp;#39;s, she is relatively attractive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/blazer2345&quot;&gt; /u/blazer2345 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m84bw/tifu_by_ruining_my_moms_friends_sweater/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m84bw/tifu_by_ruining_my_moms_friends_sweater/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m84bw</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m84bw/tifu_by_ruining_my_moms_friends_sweater/" /><updated>2018-10-07T19:49:08+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by ruining my Moms friend's sweater</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Bustyturtlelover</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Bustyturtlelover</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly NSFW, but to be safe putting that out there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This happened about a month ago, and I was tasked with helping my dad power wash our outdoor cement floor. How was I gonna help, since he was gonna be doing the actual washing with the nozzle? I was gonna hold the actual machine part still. Normally a power washer has wheels so you can roll it around and keep it in place as you wash away, but ours had its wheel break just a few weeks ago, and my father hadn&amp;#39;t gotten around to replacing it. We tried wedging wooden blocks underneath to try to keep it upright but the vibrating from the machine kept hobbling it over and off the support, and that&amp;#39;s where I came in. I needed to keep it perfectly balanced while my dad toiled away.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now here is where my mind decided to wander. It had been a while since I&amp;#39;d had a satisfactory toss of the salad, and while my hands always got the job done, I never really experienced what other girls have exclaimed with glowing reviews: vibrators are mystical. You can see where this is going.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;While my father was out of sight washing a section of the floor behind a wooden gate, I pressed my crotch up against the metal handle of the unit, and by God I was not ready for how powerful that thing was. Such relentless, jarring vibrations... it was almost too much for me to handle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Almost. I powered through, gripping that metal handle with all my might as I let it quite literally rock my body. My legs were starting to shake, my voice quivered and my legs subconsciously began pressing forward as I could feel that surge begin to heighten. I whimpered and bit my lip, my head simply swimming in the moment as I hear&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Hey whoa WHOA WHAT THE FUCK!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I took an immediate step back and looked towards the gate, seeing a massive plume of white smoke brushing over and through it as my dad barged in towards me. His eyes went to the unit, as did mine. There was smoke billowing out from its exhaust in almost frightening amounts. He took the reins and shut the machine off, grabbing it from me and looking it over while he held it. He asked me what I was doing and I meekly replied with I was just holding it forward, keeping it balanced like he asked me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apparently in my lustful throes, I was pushing the unit forward, so much forward that oil flooded the engine block and it began burning oil and fuel, hence the white smoke. As if on cue while my dad explained this to me, the exhaust port began leaking fluids, almost as much as my exhaust port but I digress. We had to stop the cleaning midwash, while my dad checked to see if I hadn&amp;#39;t fucked up the machine. I did, and now we need to buy a new one.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR I masturbated with a Power washer and through my sheer horny stupidity... we are out of a power washer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Bustyturtlelover&quot;&gt; /u/Bustyturtlelover &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m29f5/tifu_by_masturbating_with_a_power_washer/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m29f5/tifu_by_masturbating_with_a_power_washer/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m29f5</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m29f5/tifu_by_masturbating_with_a_power_washer/" /><updated>2018-10-07T03:41:43+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by Masturbating with a Power Washer.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/iwassuffocating</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/iwassuffocating</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I was thinking with my dick ( pretty much how 50% of these posts arise ). A really really really fit international chick messages me out of nowhere and starts trying to talk to me. Normally I have a pretty decent sense for these types of scams and fake accounts, but this one seemed borderline legit, because the posts/shares/pics were sorta old, and the photos looked legit and had some likes. Additionally she was super super fit ( thinking with dick). So she starts messaging me somewhat innocuously, and I think she&amp;#39;s just kinda like an odd international type looking for a friend - so I&amp;#39;m polite and message back. Part of what was so convincing was the scammer&amp;#39;s manner of messaging - they were purporting to be from Malaysia ( where my family is from), and the linguo and phrasing was totally believable which was what sold me into the ruse. Anyways she&amp;#39;s like wanna facetime? and then popsup nude (fit af). &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Long story short a scammer has a video of me jerking it with my face in it. They ask for cash and we agree on $300, which I send via western union. Unsurprisingly after that the scammer wants more money. I tell them that we are done with the whole transaction, and have since ignored their messages. Also noteworthy is that the scammer sent me screenshots- and in them they had sent photos of me with my dick out to at least one extended family member ( so i guess I&amp;#39;m no longer friends with that family member :(. They also ahve a screenshot of my wholefriends list and access to them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;tldr; scammer has a porno of me, and my friends list. They want money and have/will send more photos of my dick out to my friends list. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;IF there&amp;#39;s anything positive - I&amp;#39;ve just started excercising more recently so I kinda look good ngl. It&amp;#39;s also a little empowering to have nudes of myself out on the internet ngl. Wish my friends weren&amp;#39;t going to see it tho. also wish I wasn&amp;#39;t being harrassed. idk if this place is for advice, but advice about how to move forward, and not get upset by this whole thing would be appreciated :) I&amp;#39;ve been feeling kinda anxious and down because of this. Thanks&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/iwassuffocating&quot;&gt; /u/iwassuffocating &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdqg9/tifu_by_giving_a_scammer_an_explicit_video_and_my/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdqg9/tifu_by_giving_a_scammer_an_explicit_video_and_my/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mdqg9</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mdqg9/tifu_by_giving_a_scammer_an_explicit_video_and_my/" /><updated>2018-10-08T10:34:56+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by giving a scammer an explicit video and my friends list</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/ApathiaLol</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/ApathiaLol</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main characters in this FU are myself (34m), and POF Girl (30Ff). Supporting characters are my friends F1, F2 and F3; and her friends Dude 1 and Dude 2.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In typical fashion, this story didn&amp;#39;t take place today but rather started at the beginning of last month. I&amp;#39;m sure you can guess but I met POF Girl on Plenty Of Fish. She messaged me, we chatted for a couple days, progressed to Facebook and then by day 3 or 4 we met up to go for a walk with our dogs because it&amp;#39;s what I do every night with my dog. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;#39;m a big believer in not starting something unless it&amp;#39;s well defined or if there is an instant, undeniable attraction and chemistry. This girl was attractive, but the chemistry wasn&amp;#39;t really there. I asked her what her intentions were, she said just friends, I said ok I can do that because I like to take things slow anyway. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;By day 10 I had decided that nothing was going to happen between me and this girl (as in there was no spark on my end and that would not change), and this girl had been dropping hints that she was into me so I started coming up with a way to let her down gently. On day 14, we were hanging out at my place after a walk and she started making moves on me. I stopped her and asked her what she was doing. &amp;quot;oh nothing&amp;quot;. Uh huh. So I go on to clarify that I wasn&amp;#39;t looking for a relationship with her so therefore there would be no forward attempts on my part. She said ok and promptly left. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Obviously since this is a post in TIFU, the relationship didn&amp;#39;t end there. She immediately posted a status on Facebook about how she thought she met someone she was compatible with and was her type, only to be told we were just friends and so she was going to try her luck on a different dating website. This was red flag number one, drama queen behavior like this is why I&amp;#39;m still single. I&amp;#39;m a private person, I don&amp;#39;t need to advertise to everyone the daily goings on in my life. But whatever, it&amp;#39;s her life so she can do what she wants. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And then someone made a post about how I&amp;#39;m a douche for not seeing what she has to offer and blah blah blah. Clearly I couldn&amp;#39;t let this random person thinking I&amp;#39;m a douche, so I set the record straight. It&amp;#39;s not that there was anything wrong with this girl, it&amp;#39;s just she&amp;#39;s not what I&amp;#39;m looking for. These posts were promptly deleted.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I should have left it at that. I shouldn&amp;#39;t have done anything further. I shouldn&amp;#39;t have even commented. But again, this is TIFU so the story isn&amp;#39;t over yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A day or two later I get a message from POF Girl asking me to clarify why I wasn&amp;#39;t into her. So I did. I told her there was no spark, there was no compatibility. I didn&amp;#39;t tell her that she seemed like drama queen, she seemed a little weird, and I didn&amp;#39;t like the way she treated her dog (always called her dog stupid, which maybe was the case but I think it&amp;#39;s just because her dog lacked consistent training). After exchanging texts for a day, with me saying I&amp;#39;m kind of disappointed we can&amp;#39;t remain friends because I don&amp;#39;t mind hanging out with her plus my dog loves the company of her dog, she said she wouldn&amp;#39;t mind being &amp;quot;cuddle buddies&amp;quot;. I&amp;#39;m sure you can guess the rest of this story, but I&amp;#39;m going to tell it anyway because it&amp;#39;s so full of surprises. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So that night, day 16, I ask if she wants to join me and my dog for a walk. She asks what the plan was after? Shocking, right? Ultimately she decides to join us on our walk. Ultimately, we end up back at my place and in bed. Now, I&amp;#39;m not that dumb. I asked her if she was on birth control (no, she&amp;#39;s not. I should have packed up and went home but no, things were already heated and I&amp;#39;m a mere mortal so things were going to continue to heat up). So I wore a condom. It was dark, we had our fun, and I then went to the bathroom to clean up. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Care to guess what I found when I turned the light on? You guessed right! The condom broke. In that moment I felt complete dread. I don&amp;#39;t know why, I&amp;#39;ve been in this situation before, it was never a big deal. But this one, sheer terror. So I calmly head back to the bedroom and tell her the condom broke and ask her to get Plan B. She agrees, so I think that&amp;#39;s that. She then hops back on for round two. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At this point I&amp;#39;m thinking what I should do. Why did I feel such dread? Do I really trust this girl to get Plan B? Fuck. So I continue to let her ride me and start concentrating on not finishing again because I hadn&amp;#39;t put another condom on. Then I start thinking about something I read about a loooong while ago. The shape of the penis and why it&amp;#39;s shaped that way. I found out today that it&amp;#39;s called the semen displacement effect. Hear me out, it&amp;#39;s legit. The head of the penis creates suction and the ridge acts kind of as a squeegee. It&amp;#39;s been shown to &amp;quot;displace&amp;quot; up to 90% of semen. So all I have to do is keep going for a while, not ruin this by busting again, and I&amp;#39;ll lower the chances of having a kid with this seemingly normal woman whom I don&amp;#39;t want a relationship with. Ultimately, she stopped before she finished either because she thought I was done (to be honest I was, but I hadn&amp;#39;t finished, i just stopping putting in a lot of effort at that point). I reiterated again that she should probably get a Plan B, and then she left. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I then text F1 and F2 about my experience, because we&amp;#39;re tight like that, and because the story obviously still isn&amp;#39;t over. I tell them both that I have doubts that this girl will get Plan B and fuck my life. They obviously laugh at me and say it&amp;#39;s super awesome having kids because they both have 1 each. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I had formulated a plan to hang out with POF Girl again the next day, ask her if she got a Plan B, and if she hadn&amp;#39;t I&amp;#39;d just say hey lets go get one right now! Simple right? Of course not, because stuff came up and we couldn&amp;#39;t meet up. Same with the next night. We hung out the next night, but by then it was too late for Plan B to be effective, so I just hoped that she had gotten it or that my plan C worked. The condom also didn&amp;#39;t break this time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over the course of the next week, we never really got a chance to hang out but on Day 24 we were on the topic of birth control and future kids when she drops the bomb &amp;quot;Second one is on the way soon&amp;quot;. At this point, you can picture the &amp;quot;record scratch, freeze frame, you&amp;#39;re probably wondering how I got here&amp;quot; trope. And you&amp;#39;re right, because here&amp;#39;s where the story really gets juicy. I ask her if it&amp;#39;s mine. No response. A while later I ask if she got Plan B. Still no response. Upon the recommendation from F1, I say since she&amp;#39;s not responding, it must not be mine. Still no response.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The next day rolls around and she texts me telling me she was out with friends and I was being a jerk, but she also didn&amp;#39;t answer the fucking question. Finally, after an entire day had passed, and a few more messages were sent which consisted of her calling me a meanie for being rude or trying to take cheap jabs by asking if she should get tested, and me with various iterations of &amp;quot;is the fucking kid mine or not&amp;quot; because I’m of the opinion that that’s an entirely fucking valid question when someone hints a a new baby after the condom breaking. But she finally said &amp;#39;dont worry&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;nah&amp;quot;. She also said she had a receipt for Plan B if I wanted to see it. So all oh this is red flag number 2 to me (your foreheads are all probably fairly red at this point though). Really seems to me like she says things to get attention, which just confirms the drama queen stuff from before. So I mostly stop texting her.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She clues in to the fact that my responses have been sparce and short, so she wishes me and my dog all the best. I tell her it just seems like she says things to get attention or to just cause pain so I guess she’s right. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She still sends random messages until Day 25 when it stops because I rarely respond (I was just trying to be polite, I promise) until Day 27 when I get a Facebook Message from Dude 1 who is a random stranger to me congratulating me on the news. I like to think I’m fairly sharp, but math apparently is not my strong suit so I ignored this message because I didn’t clue in.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Day 32 I get a message from F3 at 1am asking if I know POF Girl. I say yes and ask why. Cause he also knows her from POF years ago. I ask him what he said about me, he assures me he just said we were friends and that’s it. Conversation continues with him saying she’s basically crazy and me confirming and adding that she’s pregnant and hopefully it’s not mine. F3 and F1 also know each other, and he’s into F1 but she’s not into him and F3 also knows that F1 and I also had a fling earlier this year but is aware that it didn’t go anywhere and F1 also now has a serious boyfriend. He’s still salty about it, which is entirely relevant to this story because why the fuck would it not be?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Later on in Day 32 I get a message from F1 saying her and her new BF are now probably over. Her and her BF got a message from Dude 1 basically saying me and F1 are still sleeping together and I got POF Girl pregnant. Naturally I message F3 and ask him again what he said about me. He confirms nothing, but also says to ignore everything she says because she does shit like this all time. I chalk it up to POF Girl creeping my Facebook and seeing pics of F1 and I together on a camping trip and various outings and so she’s jealous. How fucking naive I was.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I then message POF Girl and ask who Dude 1 is and why he thinks I got her pregnant? I also elaborate on the fact that I stopped talking to her because it seemed like she starts drama and I didn’t want to be involved, and this shit is proving I made the right choice. The conversation devolves very quickly with her calling me a player and I’m not her type and it’s obvious why I’m still single at 34 (bitch I called it off with you, not the other way around). She then went on to confirm more than once that the baby is someone else&amp;#39;s and she’s back with him because he actually seems like a nice guy and again accusing me of sleeping around and being rude because of the way I acted. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Day 32 was super eventful, because I also come to find out from F1 than F3 is planning on meeting up with POF chick. This blew my mind. Why would he willingly hang out with this chick who is obviously trying to ruin my life? So I ask him, and he confirms it, and says he’s basically just trying to get his dick wet. I believe him because a) POF chick seriously has it out for me at this point, and b) because I’m pretty sure he can count on one hand the amount of times he’s been laid. Also, F1 also confirmed that Dude 1 knew some details about something that only her, I, and F3 knew. It’s become clear at this point that F3 is holding a grudge and is a willing participant in POF girls plot to ostracize me from my friends. So I tell F3 that I’m sick of his shit (because he really is a sad, desperate man who only thinks of himself and will only call on you when he needs something). F1 also did the same shortly before I did.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What a fucking day. But is it over? Of course not.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Day 33, 3am, I get a message from Dude 2 telling me I’m clearly wrong, the baby is mine, and here’s some pics of positive pregnancy tests to prove it. Dude include screenshots of the details to said pics, which were taken Day 21 and Day 22 days after the deed was done. Super nice of him and I’m sure those of you keeping score at home realize that this means it was 5 and 6 days after the seed was planted. Those who took sex ed in class, and keep up on basic biology know that it’s quite unlikely that a home pregnancy kit will show as positive after a mere 5 days. Also remember how I told you all about the semen displacement effect? This makes pregnancy even less likely. Now obviously I’m not ruling out that it’s not mine, but I’m also fairly confident that if she is pregnant then it’s not mine. So like I said, super nice of Dude 2 to include screenshots of the pic details.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Because this story is already way too fucking long, and the fact that all of the characters have now been introduced and the story has already outdone any plot the writers of a high school soap opera could come up with, I’m going to summarize the next week which leads us to today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;POF girl finally admitted on Day 33 that the child is mine by way of a text stating incase I mysteriously drop off the face of the planet in 9 months, she saved my mom, brother, and sister Facebook information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She then threatened to tell my mom (I’m not even fucking joking, she literally said she was going to get her friend to message my mom) because I’m still a child and can’t take responsibility for my actions so maybe she can be an adult about it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I also sent some screenshots to Dude 2 showing that POF Girl literally told me the child was not mine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My brother and sister had already been well aware of what was going on because F2 happens to be my brother and my sister in law let it slip when we were all hanging out so I gave my sister a rundown. I then told my mom and dad about it. My dad thought it was hilarious and told me to pass POF girl his Facebook information so he could be included in the drama, so I obliged. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I theorize that POF Girl got pregnant again with baby daddy #1, realized he won’t pay child support and then tried to pin it on me thinking I wouldn’t know how babies are made or something. Either that or she’s just a bitch and in 3-4 months when it becomes painfully obvious that she’s not pregnant, she’ll claim she had a miscarriage. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for Episode 2, coming Summer 2019. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR - had sex, condom broke, girl turns out to be insane and tries to blow up my life and even threatens to get my mom involved. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/ApathiaLol&quot;&gt; /u/ApathiaLol &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mab4t/tifu_by_not_trusting_my_gut_and_it_exceeding_all/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mab4t/tifu_by_not_trusting_my_gut_and_it_exceeding_all/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mab4t</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mab4t/tifu_by_not_trusting_my_gut_and_it_exceeding_all/" /><updated>2018-10-08T00:42:40+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by not trusting my gut and it exceeding all expectations</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/M0shka</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/M0shka</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, its 11:39pm EST and I have 30 minutes to paint a good shit picture before the weekend ends so I&amp;#39;ll try to leave out embellishments. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This story happened May 2016. I was visiting America for the first time in my life and staying over at my aunt&amp;#39;s house before I started Grad school. She had just bought the house in April 2016 and it was new. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Side note: Now when I first got here, one of my goals was to look healthier and lose weight before college started so I would try make my own high-protein meals and avoid any fast-food or greasy dishes cooked at home. On one night, I had the brilliant idea of eating raw canned kidney beans for dinner. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It was also the night she was having a small party/potluck. I remember being all pretentious to people like, &amp;quot;oh sorry, but I cant eat your pizza because I&amp;#39;m trying to build some muscle&amp;quot; &lt;em&gt;gobbles spoonful of raw beans&lt;/em&gt;. Obviously, 30 minutes later, my stomach hurt like crazy and I had to excuse myself to the bathroom upstairs to unload my baggage. What ensued in the restroom was horrendous and I&amp;#39;ll spare you the details. I stood up from the toilet seat a changed man. *there was this fact I heard about everyone having 5 good shits in their life and I feel like this was one of them * &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Okay its 11:47pm I dont think I&amp;#39;m making this if i keep getting distracted, the fuck up hasn&amp;#39;t even started yet. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I try to flush the toilet and it doesnt flush but overflows. Of course. my second instinct is to flush again, because, logic, and it doesnt flush again and overflows even more. I start freaking out a bit but I&amp;#39;m also calm like okay,&amp;quot;let me just wait a bit so that the water softens the toilet paper and the poop.&amp;quot; I wash my hands and flush again and yup. One more overflow. Except, this time, the water is right at the top and starting to spill a bit. I realize that okay, I&amp;#39;m going to have to use a plunger. They didn&amp;#39;t have a plunger but they had a toilet seat cleaner so I&amp;#39;m like okay, this will have to do. I take the cleaner and try to wedge the poop down the toilet but it doesnt work. I start to panic a bit. My brother knocks on my door and I shout &amp;quot;IM BUSY&amp;quot;. He was just asking me to come for dessert but at this point I&amp;#39;m at a 100% panic mode. I start getting paranoid thinking people must think it&amp;#39;s weird that I&amp;#39;ve been gone that long. I realize that there is one thing that I can still do. I take my shirt off, take a deep breath and reach inside the bowl to squish the poop around with my hand. Yes. I did that. And I&amp;#39;m STILL NOT AT THE FUCK UP YET. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The toilet finally flushes and I&amp;#39;m like okay let me take a quick shower because what the fuck did I just do. While showering, I have this brilliant idea to use the shower head to clean the toilet seat by spraying water on it and on the floor. In my old homes, we had a drainage for water in every home so we could just guide the water on the floor into the drainage. I thought I could do that here too, so I kept &amp;quot;cleaning the toilet&amp;quot; but what I realized too late was that the water was just being accumulated on the floor and that there was no &amp;quot;drainage&amp;quot;. At this point I&amp;#39;m like fuck, let me use the toilet paper to absorb the water but that didnt work. I then tried to use the bath towels but there was just so much water. So I get dressed back downstairs and whisper to my aunt, &amp;quot;hey I spilt a bit of water on the floor in the bathroom upstairs&amp;quot; and she was like, &amp;quot;it&amp;#39;s fine, have some dessert and we&amp;#39;ll take a look at it later&amp;quot;. So I had some dessert and it was great. No one went to the bathroom upstairs (as she had 2 more downstairs) for the rest of the night and about 4 hours later, the guests started leaving. Everyone&amp;#39;s exhausted at this point. I go to check on the water hoping some of it dried up with the light, and nope, it&amp;#39;s still the same amount. So I turn on the exhaust &lt;em&gt;maybe that will help&lt;/em&gt; and go to bed thinking nothing of it since my aunt was so casual about it. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Next morning, the entire fucking room (under the bathroom) has water dripping out from the ceiling. My aunt goes &amp;quot;M0SHKA!!!!&amp;quot; I&amp;#39;ll never forget that scream. Their ceiling needed to be repainted and they had to call someone to check for mold problems too. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m over-time so I better post this quick but I can answer any questions in the comments! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tl:dr pooped in aunts house, tried to clean the toilet, ended up costing a lot of $ in damage. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/M0shka&quot;&gt; /u/M0shka &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbqby/tifu_by_taking_a_poop_and_destroying_my_aunts_new/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbqby/tifu_by_taking_a_poop_and_destroying_my_aunts_new/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mbqby</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbqby/tifu_by_taking_a_poop_and_destroying_my_aunts_new/" /><updated>2018-10-08T04:17:38+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by taking a poop and destroying my aunts new home</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/jupiterzeye</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/jupiterzeye</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened 2 years ago.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I saw a post on here about driving 5 hours and it made me think of this.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My ex lives in Florida and I live in NY. We had been together for about a year and a half or so, and when our relationship became distance, we sort of took a break. We talked about meeting up again multiple times to try and work things out, but her mobile data got shut off because she couldn’t afford her apartment, her internet, and her phone all at once. The only times I really got to talk to her about actually meeting up with her were when she would leave her apartment to get wifi or she was at work. She chose her apartment over internet and phone communication, so I was at a point where I was only texting or calling her every few days or so. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I made a rough plan with her to see her, and we were both ecstatic because it had been about 5-6 months since either of us saw each other on anything but video chats. We were still super close, even after all the shit that we had gone through. So... I get in my car and put in her address, but I have a voice in the back of my head telling me that what I’m doing is a bad idea. I choose to ignore it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I drive the 700-800 something miles it takes me to get there. I am right below her apartment when I realize that hey, maybe I don’t want to do this. After driving all those miles I’m still having doubts because I’m not sure if she actually wanted to see me or if we were just making hopeful plans for this even though both of us knew it was pretty unlikely it would happen. I had a free week and I liked roadtrips, so I didn’t think it was super out of the realm of possibility. I sat in my car, drumming on the wheel with my fingers debating if I actually wanted to get out or not before opening the door. I quickly walked up the stairs to her apartment. I notice a few papers hanging from her doorknob but don’t bother to look at them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I looked in her window to see the curtains drawn. Strange, she usually loved to have them opened. I tried to peek through to see if I could see her on the couch... but there was no couch. Huh. Strange. Her lights were on which was weird, but it told me that someone was likely there. Maybe she sold her couch to help her pay for rent. I decided to knock on her door. No response. I knock harder, still no response. I finally decide to look at the papers hanging from her doorknob. The first one I pick up...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;EVICTION NOTICE: 1/10/16&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It was the 11th. Fuck me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I go back to my car and sit with my head on the wheel for a bit. How can I be so fucking stupid? I realized that I should’ve made clear plans with her instead of banking on plans that were so rough. It was a stupid decision. I also realized that I now had to take the longest drive of shame of my life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I decided to drive 800 miles to see an ex girlfriend with whom I had sparse communication with. I got all the way to Florida before I found that she had been evicted the day before I got there. Moral of the story? Make sure your plans are clear before visiting someone far away.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/jupiterzeye&quot;&gt; /u/jupiterzeye &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m55p8/tifu_by_driving_7_states_for_nothing/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m55p8/tifu_by_driving_7_states_for_nothing/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m55p8</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m55p8/tifu_by_driving_7_states_for_nothing/" /><updated>2018-10-07T13:48:15+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by driving 7 states for nothing</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TheShadyTrader</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TheShadyTrader</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I am a guy with pretty high anxiety. Showers always seem to help a little bit and by the end of the day today I was more than ready for one. Now normally I shower in the pitch black because it&amp;#39;s nice and relaxing but for some reason today I took one with the light on.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am in the shower for a few minutes and I notice a sugar ant on the tile. I thought &amp;quot;Huh usually when theres one theres more&amp;quot; so I take a look around and sure enough they are all over the walls of my shower. Never before have I seen ants in my shower, needless to say I freak out a bit and spray them all down the drain. I thought it was a bit weird but kept on showering. Finished soaping up and went on to my sugar scrub to get the back of my arms, pelvis, etc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A few seconds later I glance down at the sugar scrub jar and notice that tons of ants had gotten inside it. Without even realizing I had ended up giving myself a horrifying exfoliating scrub of sugar, coconut oil, and ants.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Needless to say I FREAKED THE FUCK OUT.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I accidentally exfoliated myself with sugar, coconut oil, and ants...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TheShadyTrader&quot;&gt; /u/TheShadyTrader &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbh4b/tifu_in_the_shower/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbh4b/tifu_in_the_shower/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mbh4b</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbh4b/tifu_in_the_shower/" /><updated>2018-10-08T03:36:57+00:00</updated><title>TIFU In The Shower...</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/FlyingLemurs76</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/FlyingLemurs76</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened last December and hopefully some hiker somewhere learns from my near fatal mistake. Grab some popcorn, evidently I&amp;#39;m longwinded.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A background: I&amp;#39;ve hiked off and on year round for my whole life, but things picked up 18 months ago when I started going 1-2 times a week. I almost exclusively hike by myself and for sunrises. I live in New Hampshire so most of my adventures happen in the White Mountains. For those unfamiliar, our mountains play host to both extreme cold and wind. Mount Washington routinely exceeds 100 mph wind gusts in any season and drops lower than -100F with windchill in winter. It holds a few wind records and I&amp;#39;d recommend reading the wiki on it. Anyway its a blast and well worthwhile for the knowledgable/prepared.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The story: I started hiking that day after a slightly delayed start. The temperature at the trailhead was -9F, so cold but doable. I go across the three peaks I wanted to and start on my way back. Canadian Jay&amp;#39;s perched on snow laden boughs of evergreen, a meandering path trodden in the snow, minimal people, all the stuff that I love. The sun starts setting. Not a big deal, I hike in the dark all the time. I go for my headlamp but it wont turn on. I replaced the batteries before my trip, it simply wont turn on. Throw the spares in the headlamp, round two is still a no-go. Try the back up headlamp, nope. Emergency flashlight? Still a no. Phone? Murdered by the cold. The suns setting, I&amp;#39;m still 5 miles from my car, by now its -15F and dropping, 20 mph winds to boot, and I&amp;#39;m by myself. I remember a ladder section a mile below the summit that is literally packed with snow and ice, that&amp;#39;s not something to navigate by a sliver of moonlight. So I &amp;quot;perform a seated glissade&amp;quot;, or a sat on my butt and sledded down the steep bits. The ladder section ends near simultaneously with the remaining light.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I cant see the trail well and the wind is blowing snow back into it. I&amp;#39;m pushing with my feet to find the path of least resistance. I&amp;#39;m so cold but I dont feel it, beyond shivering like a jackhammer. I&amp;#39;m stumbling, mumbling, and incoherently grunting for no reason. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is where I hit a critical point. If I keep going and end up off trail, a search and rescue attempt probably wouldnt find me until it was too late. If I stop and curl up in a bivy, I lose the heat from moving and I could die before search and rescue could find me. It was so tempting, I can&amp;#39;t explain it but laying down seemed like such a pleasant idea. I kept going for the remaining miles. By the time i get back to my car in the empty lot, I can&amp;#39;t form a coherent thought other than car=heat. I set my car to 85F and drive the two hours home. I still feel the cold deep in my core and that is one of the weirdest sensations to try to describe. Like if you eat an ice cube on a really hot day you can feel the cold in your stomach, but this is a bit lower and radiates the cold out to the rest of you. It sits deep in the pit of your body. An hour long hot shower after two cups of hot coco couldn&amp;#39;t get me warm, I cacooned in 3 quilts until the next day just to shake it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I still hike solo in the winter but for sunrises so I start in the dark instead of ending in it. I also carry an excessive pack so I can survive a night out there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Looking back and reading up on hypothermia, if I had taken another 1-3 hours on that hike or if I decided to stash in that bivy I probably wouldnt be here to post this story. At the least, I would have been unconscious by the time my gf (ex now, unrelated) got a search and rescue team contacted. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I was hiking in very cold weather, electronics failed at sunset, and I get hypothermic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/FlyingLemurs76&quot;&gt; /u/FlyingLemurs76 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbypp/tifu_by_not_understanding_how_extreme_cold/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbypp/tifu_by_not_understanding_how_extreme_cold/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mbypp</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mbypp/tifu_by_not_understanding_how_extreme_cold/" /><updated>2018-10-08T04:56:16+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by not understanding how extreme cold affects electronics, almost fatally</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/finnyfiin</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/finnyfiin</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened at the start of the year. Excuse the terrible grammar as it’s on my phone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So basically there I was, on holiday and enjoying my long awaited Christmas leave. A bit of context, so I passed an officer selection board and instead of going straight into the officer training I wanted to do recruit basic training and see what it’s like to be a soldier first and realise the hardships that they go through. This went on for all of last year and it was some of the best and worst times of my life but that’s another story. Throughout the year I was asked what I wanted to do with my career, and I explained to them that I was meant to be doing officer training next year and they were cool about it surprisingly. I was told that everything was in place and I would transition smoothly to the following years officer training. Well throughout the year I heard nothing. Not a single thing. Not an email. Nothing. It was allgood I thought. Then it came to December and I was due to start in January. So I booked my leave ‘trusting’ the system and took a months leave to enjoy the break. I even took a special trip into work to use the secure computers to check my email. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nothing....&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now I started to panic. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I ended up messaging a LT I knew from a course and he told me to go and see this lady Karen.. Well fuck me guess what? karen was still on leave and I cut my leave a week early just to try and sort it out only to find the camp empty (I drove a long way from family to get back to base) so I spent the week in panic and it was useless. The following Monday (the course has started) I go into see the boss and explain the situation and he calls Higher HQ. They have NOTHING in the system about me doing officer training. Luckily, I kept my papers I signed and upon showing the boss he was on the phone all day to HQ trying to figure out who fucked it up. HQ finally said it was their fault on Tuesday morning and that I could come back in 2019 as the course had already started. My boss (great guy) ended up telling HQ to fuck off and get me down there as I hadn’t missed much, that Tuesday afternoon I was told to pack my bags. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Well fuck me, I had to get my camp clearances signed off by EVERYONE important in the camp, I was a simple private having to seek everyone high up that afternoon and then had to sign over a lot of my units kit to the Q-Store, as well as empty my ENTIRE room into my car.. all within the space of a mere 3-4 hours. The Wednesday morning I had to get a final signature, drop off a key then I was driven to the airport without saying goodbye to anyone and flown down to start the course 3 days late. I had to leave my car and everything else at that camp and it was a huge cluster fuck in my life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I fucked my family, HQ and myself around all because I hadn’t had the balls to ask what was happening before I went on Christmas leave. But it’s all over now and I’ll be graduating at the end of the year. That was perhaps the most stressful and most life changing moment of my life all because I had no nuts and trusted the system. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR I didn’t tell my command chain I was meant to be doing officer training which meant I fucked everyone around and created the most stressful time of my life for myself because I had no balls to check it was allgood.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/finnyfiin&quot;&gt; /u/finnyfiin &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mddfb/tifu_by_not_telling_my_command_chain_i_was_meant/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mddfb/tifu_by_not_telling_my_command_chain_i_was_meant/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9mddfb</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9mddfb/tifu_by_not_telling_my_command_chain_i_was_meant/" /><updated>2018-10-08T09:27:38+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by not telling my command chain I was meant to be doing officer training</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/wrenchy-_-</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/wrenchy-_-</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yesterday I was out with a couple of friends who had weed with them and I smoked about two huge joints. After the second one I was feeling terrible and really anxious but I had to go. My heart was beating like crazy and I needed to walk about 2km to get home and I almost got hit twice by a car. I was so stoned that I even went to a random man on the street and telling him “I did something bad, I smoked weed and I’m feeling ultra sick like almost dying” he just said “don’t worry man I smoke weed too you’ll be fine no one died just go for a walk”. I kept telling him that I’m almost ready to pass out and he kept telling me you’re fine. I thought to myself this is getting nowhere so I kept walking home. I couldn’t focus on the street and my mind just went crazy thinking about stuff and I was lost to the thoughts like i had no vision but mechanically walking. I went straight to bed (luckily only my father was home and he was watching sports so I just said hey I’m really tired I’m going to bed. And he believed me.) After about two hours of being in bed I managed to sleep. Fast forward today I went to school feeling some effects of the weed still in my body. Two to three hours on school passed and I was feeling dizzy so I asked to go out of the class and get some air. I called my parents and said that I am really dizzy and I need to go home. Now in about two hours I have to go to the doctor because my parents are worried. I’m worried what I’m going to tell the doctor. Ugh guys worst decision in my life!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TLDR: smoked weed, had to walk 2km stoned and almost dead. Next day I felt sick and now I have a doctors’s appointment to see what’s wrong although it is from the weed .&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/wrenchy-_-&quot;&gt; /u/wrenchy-_- &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me2wp/tifu_i_smoked_weed_and_now_im_in_a_difficult/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me2wp/tifu_i_smoked_weed_and_now_im_in_a_difficult/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9me2wp</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me2wp/tifu_i_smoked_weed_and_now_im_in_a_difficult/" /><updated>2018-10-08T11:36:12+00:00</updated><title>TIFU I smoked weed and now I’m in a difficult situation.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/jargson</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/jargson</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obligatory this actually happened 14 years ago but it has been haunting me more over the last year since the #MeToo movement began, especially with Louis CK. So I was 18 and a freshman in college living in an apartment with my best friend. We had a common female friend whom we talked with often on AIM (Instant Messenger for people too young to remember) and she also went to college nearby. One day, I forget the circumstances as to why she came over, but she came to our apartment one day while my roommate was out and the topic of conversation somehow ended up being the Paris Hilton sex tape that was recently released. I was a virgin at the time and she was a bit more experienced than me at the time and I was attracted to her and had very little sense of what is appropriate when alone with a girl and the topic is porn. She asked me to pull up the video on my laptop so I did and we actually watched it together for a couple minutes before she asked &amp;quot;do you have an erection?&amp;quot; and I think I said &amp;quot;Yeah&amp;quot; and she asked &amp;quot;Well wouldn&amp;#39;t you be masturbating if I weren&amp;#39;t here?&amp;quot; and I kind of laughed and said &amp;quot;Yeah I guess maybe&amp;quot; and she said &amp;quot;So why don&amp;#39;t you just do it now anyway?&amp;quot; and I said &amp;quot;That would be weird.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Only if you make it weird.&amp;quot; So I actually took my penis out, began masturbating for literally 3 or 5 seconds or so, and became embarrassed and stopped. Still aroused, I went in the bathroom and &amp;quot;finished&amp;quot; and I think I told her I just went in there to go to the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In hindsight, I think I grossly misnavigated that entire situation. I haven&amp;#39;t talked to her since because I think she told her friends and some of my friends I &amp;quot;jerked off&amp;quot; in front of her and I felt that was somewhat of an unfair description because that implies she didn&amp;#39;t ask me to? If I could re do it I would just not ever bring my dick out and not ever pull up that website since really I had not a lot of interest in the girl besides thinking she was attractive and me being a young dumb virgin (honestly, I probably had more interest in her than her &amp;quot;just being attractive&amp;quot;, but since she was a mutual friend I knew I couldn&amp;#39;t pursue her romantically). However, with the Louis CK and Brett Kavanaugh stuff I definitely have an increased guilty conscience from this after all these years later. Now, I&amp;#39;m married and have kids and I&amp;#39;m pretty terrified of ever running in to her again even though I&amp;#39;m hoping she doesn&amp;#39;t even care that it happened? She&amp;#39;s tried adding me on Facebook and other social media sites multiple times since then and I was too embarrassed to accept the request. I wish I would have just talked to her about it like that same week that it happened forever ago and just said &amp;quot;Wow that was dumb of me, I&amp;#39;m really sorry&amp;quot; even though part of me also feels like she kind of wanted me to do it? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I consider myself a feminist and this weighs heavy on me since I&amp;#39;m afraid I did something wrong but I&amp;#39;m also afraid of talking to her since I&amp;#39;m not even sure if it bothers her. Ugh&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR I took my dick out while alone with a girl, thought for a second it was somehow appropriate, then immediately put it back in, have had shame ever since&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/jargson&quot;&gt; /u/jargson &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me20j/tifu_by_exposing_myself_when_i_thought_it_was/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me20j/tifu_by_exposing_myself_when_i_thought_it_was/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9me20j</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9me20j/tifu_by_exposing_myself_when_i_thought_it_was/" /><updated>2018-10-08T11:31:50+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by exposing myself when I thought it was appropriate</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/missinglink242</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/missinglink242</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tifu in question was yesterday. Recently I got hired at a bank and things were running smoothly. I had learned all the procedures and security protocols that come along with working around so much money. One day, I was asked to work a Saturday. I&amp;#39;m fairly new and I didn&amp;#39;t know what to expect so I came in kinda early. I arrived to work at 9:00 a.m. Apparently, Saturdays start late (around 10:30 a.m.) in comparison to normal week days (which I didn&amp;#39;t know at the time). The security guard was there so I assumed the area was open for us employees to get in. I used my key to get through the secured doors that lead to my department. As soon as I unlocked the last door, I noticed two things. 1. There&amp;#39;s NOONE in the department. 2. THE ALARM IS FUCKING WAILING. I tried not to panic, I walked back out the secured doors and sit in the lunchroom for a while. Then my boss comes in. We&amp;#39;re having regular conversation y&amp;#39;know like welcome to your first saturday etc. Then I subtly drop in this little gem, &amp;quot;Oh btw, i went inside the department and noone was there and now the door is making a funny sound&amp;quot;. Her:&amp;quot;....You went all the way inside?...&amp;quot; Me:&amp;quot;Mhm&amp;quot; I&amp;#39;ve never seen that woman run so fucking fast until i said that. Long story short, she disabled the alarm, the security guard spoke with the alarm company and prevented the fucking police from coming and arresting my black ass. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I came to work too early and ended up setting off an alarm and almost getting arrested/fired.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/missinglink242&quot;&gt; /u/missinglink242 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m7f0l/tifu_by_setting_off_a_bank_alarm/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m7f0l/tifu_by_setting_off_a_bank_alarm/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m7f0l</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m7f0l/tifu_by_setting_off_a_bank_alarm/" /><updated>2018-10-07T18:30:23+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by setting off a bank alarm</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/huntstheman</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/huntstheman</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I cannot believe how much of a screw up I am. I do not deserve the air I breath. I’m sorry if this is poorly written as I am extremely hungover. Some context is that we are all underage, 16 to be exact. Our parents don’t know we have ever drank, and didn’t know of our drinking intentions. Last night was my friends birthday (let’s call him R) and we wanted to have some fun. Me, R, a guy we will call JJ, and my best friend (M) wanted to drink to celebrate R’s birthday. I bought a 1750ml bottle of Vodka for us. I decided a fun place to do it would be in the middle of a field, and we could crash in my car afterwards. Between me, R, JJ, and M, we shared the vodka all night. I drank enough to not remember a single damn thing, so the events I will explain will be from my friends description along with the paramedics, my father, the police, and R (who was the most sober of all of us). &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It started when I purchased the alcohol from my friend who’s name isn’t important. At the time I felt like nothing bad would happen to me. Me and R (it was R’s birthday) messed around at my house until JJ and M arrived. I promised my dad we were just going to R’s house. We went to the field, parked my car, and began to drink. It started great, everyone was having a good time. The more we drank, the less we could control ourselves. Let me remind you that R wasn’t hitting the bottle too hard. From here my memory is hazy. By 1am, my best fucking friend M was on the floor, unconscious, throwing up constantly. Luckily my friend R saw him, and freaked out. He started by using my phone to call my friend S. S and his mom drove over and woke up my parents, called the police and paramedics, and got them to the field. JJ and R were taken to my house by my dad to sleep. The cops questioned me, found drugs in my car, but didn’t take me in. M was rushed to the emergency room and they had found he had a blood alcohol content of 0.26% (you are legally drunk after 0.08%). My dad took me home. I had thrown up all over myself, and so had my friends. My dad put me in my room to sleep. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All of our parents had no idea any of us ever drank. They were oblivious to what our plans were, so you can imaging there shock. If it weren’t for my friend S and his mom, and especially R for called them, I could have killed my best friend. My best fucking friend. Obviously I received hell for this (I completely deserve it). M has to pay the hospital bills, I am grounded until college, and most importantly, I can’t be in my band anymore.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR- My friends and I drank, a lot, and my best friend almost died of alcohol poisoning.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/huntstheman&quot;&gt; /u/huntstheman &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m83po/tifu_by_almost_killing_my_best_friend_with/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m83po/tifu_by_almost_killing_my_best_friend_with/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m83po</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m83po/tifu_by_almost_killing_my_best_friend_with/" /><updated>2018-10-07T19:47:05+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by almost killing my best friend with alcohol poisoning</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/birkenstocksNsocks</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/birkenstocksNsocks</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was just a few hours ago...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I was really thirsty while watching Netflix, so I got up and made my way through the dark into the kitchen for a drink of water.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I grabbed a cup from the cupboard, filled it up with the water from the fridge, then started drinking.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About halfway through, I felt a chunk of something in my mouth, thinking it was some food that didn&amp;#39;t wash off in the dishwasher, I spit it out in the sink. I turned on the light to see what it was, and there, in the sink, was A FUCKING SPIDER. I immediately gagged, screamed, then did the heebie jeebie dance while crying then gagging some more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After several minutes of crying, I drove myself to get ice cream. I&amp;#39;m still gagging thinking about it. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TLDR: Got a drink of water in the dark, felt a chunk, spat it out. Chunk = spider.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Video in comments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Edit: clarifying that I drank the spider. Spider was in my mouth. I felt it with my tongue. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/birkenstocksNsocks&quot;&gt; /u/birkenstocksNsocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m34r5/tifu_by_drinking_water_in_the_dark/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m34r5/tifu_by_drinking_water_in_the_dark/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m34r5</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m34r5/tifu_by_drinking_water_in_the_dark/" /><updated>2018-10-07T06:28:02+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by drinking water in the dark</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Dr_IDG4F</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Dr_IDG4F</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course like anything on here this happened a while back, around 5-6 years ago. But since I have just created a throwaway account mainly to browse and comment on NSFW subs, I said &amp;#39;why the hell not?&amp;#39;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Back during undergrad I started dating this chick I had met in my chem class. She was gorgeous and we matched in every way, even sexually. We were getting it on maybe 2-3 times a day; you know, the regular frequency you get when first start dating. We would some times do it at school, in the library after hours or in the bathroom. She was a total freak! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So to the fuck up part. One day during finals, we both get super horny and decide to take a break from studying. Problem was, campus was full of students due to finals and we thought it would be difficult to find a place. So I get this genius idea to rent a zip car for an hour, drive to her house (which was 10-15 min away), bang and then drive back. What could go wrong right? So I get a Zipcar and needless to say during the entire drive she is teasing me and making me more excited. We rush to her place, find parking spot in front of her apartment (which was super odd considering it was super difficult to find parking around there at any given time, but I didn&amp;#39;t think anything of it since I was in full on reproduction mode. Leave the car, go to her place and boom! SEX! I remember being amazing; in fact so great I busted inside. She loved it! I said &amp;quot;fuck it, I&amp;#39;ll get one of those plan B&amp;#39;s or what not&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show is over, we clean up, laugh at the whole thing and how desperate we looked and as we walk out we found that our Zipcar vehicle wasn&amp;#39;t there. I immediately freak the fuck out as the first thing I thought was: the car was stolen! &amp;quot;No it wasn&amp;#39;t, it was towed!&amp;quot; - a dude yelled across the street. &amp;quot;This street is closed for an event, look at this sign&amp;quot; and there it was, a no parking sign for a park event that I completely missed due to being blinded with thoughts of sex. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I spent the next 2-3 hours calling zip car and the police department as I had no idea how to go about fixing this whole thing. To make things worse, I had no idea where the car had been taken and the PD were not helpful given the fact this wasn&amp;#39;t registered under my name! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fast forward to 7-8 hours later I find the lot where they took the car to, pay the fees and return it to the drop off location. I also had to pay a large fee to Zipcar . I think I dropped like 700-900 that day. For a student this is freaking a lot! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anyway, I get home after a long ass day close to midnight, and pass the fuck out... I&amp;#39;m glad shit is over...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;NO!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She texted me the following afternoon telling me we forgot about something important. The freaking plan B! I had just spent almost 1k on being stupid I was not gonna bring a baby to to this planet, so I borrow my roommates car, go to CVS get one of those pills and have her take it. She took it almost 24hours after our last sexual act! And the waiting game was the freaking worse! I have never waited for blood this anxiously and hope I never have to ever again! Wear condoms fellas! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR rented a car to fuck my girl, busted inside of her, got the car towed and almost got her pregnant cause i forgot to get her the pill on time. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Dr_IDG4F&quot;&gt; /u/Dr_IDG4F &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m6cdb/tifu_by_getting_my_zipcar_towed_and_almost/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m6cdb/tifu_by_getting_my_zipcar_towed_and_almost/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m6cdb</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m6cdb/tifu_by_getting_my_zipcar_towed_and_almost/" /><updated>2018-10-07T16:26:22+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by getting my Zipcar towed and almost getting my GF prego</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/newyork_sucks</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/newyork_sucks</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title Edit: &amp;quot;Now scared for my life&amp;quot; ------TLDR: Stumbled into room of people with guns , swastikas, and the groom during the reception. I left with a big mouth telling a few out of concern.Ruined wedding night.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Am now Worried for my life.------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I guess I&amp;#39;ll have to begin with a moral dilemma. Is there ever a wrong time time to out a racist? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It wasn&amp;#39;t my intention to be honest .&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I just walked into the wrong room with the wrong people, one of whom was the groom holding a military grade assault weapon. (this was during a lull in the reception mind you)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He held A beautiful AR by the looks of it....oh and a few swastikas emblazoned on the back wall of a rifle display case.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It wasn&amp;#39;t the guns or the emblems that frightened me however, it was the manner in which I was surrounded as I exchange some pleasantries about the firearms with them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I felt a serious notion that I was about to be intimidated into silencing myself OR ELSE.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But in a moment of relief, a brides maid walked into the predicament and even her herself exclaimed, &amp;quot;we&amp;#39;ll this doesn&amp;#39;t look right at all&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I used this moment to excuse myself from the room after avoiding plaving my prints on the firearms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I grabbed my wife and made it towards the exit. I said my farewells along the way and when asked why so soon, I told them of my findings. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I did not feel comfortable staying and I advised them to consider staying only if they felt they were comfortable doing so given the knowledge is shared.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I left and drove home with my wife.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Flash forward to 11:45pm upon my arrival home just a few minutes ago.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I spoke with my sister&amp;#39;s whom inform me of massive drama unfolding after our departure. Including the bride defending her husband&amp;#39;s right to bare swastikas because, &amp;quot;Its not like any of us are jews!)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Words were exchanged. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;People left. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The wedding came to a close.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;.......&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, I fear I may face greater repercussions in the form of retaliation. I don&amp;#39;t know what to do, and I am genuinely concerned for the safety of my wife and my self at the hands of armed, angry, pissed off groom and groomsmen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Any advise would be nice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/newyork_sucks&quot;&gt; /u/newyork_sucks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m2w7q/tifu_by_outing_my_friends_husband_as_a_gun_toting/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m2w7q/tifu_by_outing_my_friends_husband_as_a_gun_toting/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m2w7q</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m2w7q/tifu_by_outing_my_friends_husband_as_a_gun_toting/" /><updated>2018-10-07T05:40:22+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by outing my friend's husband as a gun toting, swastika flying racist....during their wedding reception. No scared for my life.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/adamkaas</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/adamkaas</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had some leftover beef stew my mom made yesterday so I thought I&amp;#39;d cook some rice while my parents arent home. Found an already open bag, and started cooking it. Everything went good, I enjoyed the meal... until.. there was very little rice left when I noticed a few &amp;quot;grayer&amp;quot; grains. I inspected them and found out that they were F*%!NG worms. Not gonna lie, I got a bit nervous, went and checked the bag of rice and it was full of small gray worms, I still don&amp;#39;t how how did I not see them the first time... Called my mom, she said they opened that bag of rice a couple years ago they just forgot to throw it out... So yeah, somehow I don&amp;#39;t feel like eating rice again for a while..&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL:DR: Didn&amp;#39;t notice that I made expired rice which had worms in it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/adamkaas&quot;&gt; /u/adamkaas &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m3mnd/tifu_by_accidentally_eating_a_handful_of_worms/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m3mnd/tifu_by_accidentally_eating_a_handful_of_worms/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m3mnd</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m3mnd/tifu_by_accidentally_eating_a_handful_of_worms/" /><updated>2018-10-07T08:25:01+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by accidentally eating a handful of worms.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Zaynarito</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Zaynarito</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night I got super high with my buddy and went to see a movie we’ve been waiting for. We bought way too much food and 2 sodas. I was walking down the aisle of A PACKED theater, and I dropped my buddy’s soda on this guy sitting in the lower aisle. The entire Fruitopia fountain drink fell on this guy’s neck, down his black shirt, his seat, and splashed his gf. He stood up and stared at me and shook his head. His gf got up and just stared at him. I kept saying “I am so sorry!”. I handed him all my napkins, and said “I am going to come back for you.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I contemplated leaving my buddy and walking out of the theater and jumping in front of a bus. I went and sat down in my assigned seat to think. I got up and went to the side and took off my black shirt. I was wearing 3 layers. I folded my shirt nicely, put on my sweater and jacket and walked over to him. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He was sitting with just an unbuttoned jacket on, I handed him my shirt and said I don’t know what else to do, man, I am really sorry. He smiled and said it’s okay, you didn’t mean to do it. And took the shirt. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TLDR; I dropped a Fruitopia on a guy while walking to my seat at the movie theater. Ended up giving him my shirt.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Zaynarito&quot;&gt; /u/Zaynarito &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lyvqg/tifu_by_embarrassing_myself_at_the_movie_theater/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lyvqg/tifu_by_embarrassing_myself_at_the_movie_theater/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9lyvqg</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lyvqg/tifu_by_embarrassing_myself_at_the_movie_theater/" /><updated>2018-10-06T19:44:54+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by embarrassing myself at the movie theater.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/desireewhitehall</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/desireewhitehall</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one took awhile, but oh GOD does it feel like it belongs here!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So awhile ago I bought a watermelon. Cheap, yummy, all that good stuff. I don&amp;#39;t remember &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; I sat it out to cut it, only &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; I sat it out to cut it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And life comes at you fast, as they say.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My mother has been having a rough time with the newly-single life, and most of my time has been spent either with her and my sister, or with taking care of things they no longer feel comfortable with leaving around their home (paperwork, old belongings, etc). This culminated in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9ltc1n/tifu_by_taking_out_a_couchand_the_back_stairs&quot;&gt;separate TIFU&lt;/a&gt; yesterday.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cue today, I wake up and step out into my own living room and into a swarm of gnats you&amp;#39;d see forming an evil portal in a horror movie. And I&amp;#39;m trying to figure out what I could have possibly left out since I went to bed without dinner.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I break out the most environmentally-unfriendly spray I&amp;#39;ve got, and proced to unleash a cloud of sweet, sweet lung cancer into the room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At first, nothing looks out of place. Pile of paperwork, couple of heavy objects, no food or anything. And all I can smell is my brain cells dying.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I start moving shit off my sadly-cluttered couch. Heavy objects find a place in the floor, and papers start to be moved to the end table.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s when the most overwhelming smell of vomit and catshit hits my nose.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I move a few more (thankfully useless) papers and come across what looks like bad cat puke.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Found the source of the bug problem!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I grab my gloves, paper towels, and cleaner, and as I&amp;#39;m throwing away chuncks of sickly red and brown I start think that this is too deep and neat a burial job for my cat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then I find an oddly-solid bottom to all of it. I lift it up to inspect it. It&amp;#39;s green, striped, and falling apart. I have no clue what it is. It looks vaguely like a...like a...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Oh, &lt;em&gt;fuck&lt;/em&gt;! Watermelon!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And it has been ripening and rotting for a good month and a half. And I let heavy mementos split it open. And I feel like a lazy slob.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My sweet day of doing nothing is ruined...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR I successfully converted a watermelon into a rottermelon. Yay, science!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/desireewhitehall&quot;&gt; /u/desireewhitehall &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lwk3j/tifu_by_hatching_a_watermelon/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lwk3j/tifu_by_hatching_a_watermelon/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9lwk3j</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lwk3j/tifu_by_hatching_a_watermelon/" /><updated>2018-10-06T15:00:08+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by hatching a watermelon</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/carcigenicate</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/carcigenicate</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened about half an hour ago.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My sister recently got me a bottle of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.ca/Bomb-Beyond-Insanity-Hot-Sauce/dp/B000FIBBWS/ref=sr_1_1/137-9462479-8096529?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1538871238&amp;amp;sr=8-1&amp;amp;keywords=da%27+bomb+hot+sauce&quot;&gt;Da Bomb&lt;/a&gt; hot sauce as a gift since she knows I love spicy food, and the YouTube channel Hot Ones that uses this particular sauce.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For dinner tonight, I decided to make up some canned soup, and was in the mood for some hot sauce. I dumped two good sized drops of Da Bomb into the soup, then nuked it for a bit. I took it out and couldn&amp;#39;t smell the hot sauce at all, so I added some more. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I started eating it, and it was &lt;em&gt;hot&lt;/em&gt;, but manageable. On my ~5th spoonful though, some of the fumes from the hot sauce irritated my nose while I was eating, and I inhaled a bit, which caused me to choke a bit on the spicy soup. I started coughing, which spread the soup all over the back of my throat and a little managed to get up into my sinuses.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This sucked, but would have been OK if I had left it alone. For some reason though, my immediate reaction was to run and blow my nose. &lt;em&gt;Don&amp;#39;t do this&lt;/em&gt;, if that isn&amp;#39;t already obvious. All that did was force the hot sauce through my nose, burning the inside of my nostrils, and giving me a nose bleed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;That&lt;/em&gt; hurt (and still does; a lot). I&amp;#39;m sitting here, sweat dripping down my face, writing this in an attempt to distract myself from the fact that the inside of my face feels like it&amp;#39;s on fire. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I stupidly choked on and blew through my nose extraordinarily hot hot sauce, giving me a nose bleed and setting the inside of my head on fire.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/carcigenicate&quot;&gt; /u/carcigenicate &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m118u/tifu_by_blowing_my_nose_after_choking_on_hot_sauce/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m118u/tifu_by_blowing_my_nose_after_choking_on_hot_sauce/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m118u</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m118u/tifu_by_blowing_my_nose_after_choking_on_hot_sauce/" /><updated>2018-10-07T00:30:12+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by blowing my nose after choking on hot sauce</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/SheZowRaisedByWolves</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/SheZowRaisedByWolves</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This happened a few years ago.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I was home sick with the flu during the flu at this time. My dad brought me some chili from a certain sassy fast food chain on his lunch break before going back to work. After I was done eating and lying on the couch, I started to feel that rumbly sensation in my stomach. The kind where I know there won&amp;#39;t be a warning gag, just straight puke. I wasn&amp;#39;t close enough to the bathroom to make it there in time, but I remember how people in cartoons/movies puke into paper bags when they&amp;#39;re on planes. I grabbed the greasy paper bag (since my dad got food for himself too) and fired away into it. Almost immediately, I remembered cartoon physics vs real-life physics. So they vomit piled up at the bottom and tore through pretty much instantly. I was mortified, but seeing the puke just made me puke more. I was in a gridlock of sick, unable to move from my spot. The bottom of the bag was nonexistent by now and my lunch was oozing off my couch cushions. I held it together long enough to throw the bag away and grab some wipes and febreeze. Feeling my chunky vomit from beneath the wipes sent me into another puking fit and I sprayed more onto the carpet. I ended up using a lot of wipes and nearly the entire can of spray to mask the smell, but there are still stains on the cushions and carpet to this day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Paper bag gave out and I threw up on my couch.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/SheZowRaisedByWolves&quot;&gt; /u/SheZowRaisedByWolves &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m132z/tifu_by_puking_into_a_paper_bag/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m132z/tifu_by_puking_into_a_paper_bag/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m132z</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m132z/tifu_by_puking_into_a_paper_bag/" /><updated>2018-10-07T00:38:05+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by puking into a paper bag</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/zebberman</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/zebberman</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok this actually happened about 25 years ago when I was 14. Not sure exactly how this is done (PLEASE DON’T TRY THIS) but we heard of a way to make yourself pass out and thought for some reason it would be cool to do it at my house. I bent down on the ground and took 10 deep breaths, on the tenth breath I stood up and then my friend behind me would lift me up bear hugging around my chest and hold me in the air and then set me down. The last thing I remember saying is “it didn’t wor......” and then boom I crashed to the ground. Of all the crazy things to happen and I still don’t exactly even understand how it did I somehow fell on a metal doorknob that was taken apart on the floor. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The door was broken and for some reason I don’t know how but one part of the knob was somehow facing up and was long and skinny and I fell right upon it and it went through my lip! I instantly woke up and blood was everywhere and I was crying and confused as all hell. My parents were in the other room and freaked out and rushed me to the ER. To this day I still never told them what really happened to me...they think it was a wrestling accident.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heard of a way to make yourself pass out, decided to try it. Took 10 deep breaths, my friend lifted me in the air and set me down and then I passed out and fell on a broken doorknob that went through my lip. Blood everywhere, went to ER. Never told my parents what really happened.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/zebberman&quot;&gt; /u/zebberman &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lw31u/tifu_by_deciding_to_have_my_friend_make_me_pass/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lw31u/tifu_by_deciding_to_have_my_friend_make_me_pass/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9lw31u</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9lw31u/tifu_by_deciding_to_have_my_friend_make_me_pass/" /><updated>2018-10-06T13:51:41+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by deciding to have my friend make me pass out and have a broken doorknob go through my lip.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/UpTheMightyReds</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/UpTheMightyReds</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obligatory this happened about 6 years ago...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, I ran in to the girl involved today, which reminded me of this episode and I thought this place is the perfect place to tell. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;First of all, I’ll explain about the circumcision. When I was growing up, I was never able to pull my foreskin over the head of my penis. I knew this was strange from my porn watching during my teenage years. I was still able to urinate and masturbate fine, so I figured it was a problem for another day as I was ridiculously embarrassed about going the doctor and showing them what was wrong. I lost my virginity when I was 17 and luckily, the girl did not look at my penis once and know what was wrong. After this, I knew I needed to get it sorted as I couldn’t have any girl look at my ugly ass dick. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So. I went the doctors and was referred to a specialist and eventually I got booked in for a circumcision. The operation went fine, but my dick was incredibly painful as I had the most sensitive head of penis that has ever been known to man. As it had been covered up for 18 years, it never saw the light of day and had the chance to desensitise. It was pretty painful anyway due to the stitches and trauma, but this made it pretty unbearable. It was only a day surgery, so I was told I could go home that night with some very clear advice. “Refrain from sexual activities for 3-4 weeks”. I said that’s fine and thought I couldn’t anyway...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I had turned 18 by this point and had moved into university halls, so after the op my flat mate picked me up and took me back there. The next few days were horrible, as I was struggling to wear underwear. Each slight movement of my dick against my boxers burned like hell, due to my super sensitive penis head. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then comes the weekend and the fuck up. I had been talking to a girl on and off for a few weeks, who also lives on the same hall site, but in a different flat to me. I knew she was quite into me, as the way she was talking to me was extremely flirty and I was pretty sure she wanted to sleep with me. She joked the previous week about coming back to my for flat after a night out. It was pretty late and I was texting her, and all of a sudden I get a call from her and she said to me that she is locked out of her flat as she went out without her keys. She was already stood outside my flat. Straight away I have numerous things flying round my head. The first being that I can’t say no to her coming in. The second being, what if she touches my dick?? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So anyway, I let her in. She was a little drunk but not that bad. We end up getting into bed and talking for a bit, we start spooning and turn the light off to go to sleep. At this point I’m thinking crisis averted and I thought that she was just going to go to sleep. Little was I wrong. She starts pushing her cute little bum backwards and grinding slowly. I get an instant boner and it’s pretty painful. It wasn’t quite as bad as earlier in the week, but it wasn’t healed by any means. She keeps doing things to try and turn me on and giving me signals to make a move. I end up kissing her and she starts touching me. It was painful but it felt so good and me being the horny 18 year old that I was, I think fuck it and carried on with the foreplay. I went down on her and then she started moaning that she wanted me to fuck her. Without a second thought, I grab a condom, put it on (with some great difficulty) and go for it with me on top. It felt good but it was sore too. I don’t last very long as my dick is super sensitive as I say, and I think that I’ve gotten through it without any accidents. She seems to enjoy it. We then lie back down and spoon again until she falls asleep. I then went the bathroom and checked my dick as I was worried. I was horrified to find that some of the stitches had split and there was quite a lot of blood. I try to clean up what I could and try to sleep. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The next morning things are pretty sore, but I think that everything will be okay in a few days and things will recover. The next day, things are a lot worse and it gets to the point that I have to go back the hospital. I get there and they say it looks badly infected and it needed stitching up again. I end up staying there for 2 nights! When I look back on it now I laugh at how incredibly stupid I was and I can’t believe that I got myself in that situation. 10/10 though I’d probably do it again. Hope you enjoyed that harrowing tale&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: I had a circumcision, ended up in bed with a hot girl a few days later, had sex because 18 year old me was to stupid and horny to say no, split my stitches and ended up in hospital for 2 nights with a badly infected dick. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/UpTheMightyReds&quot;&gt; /u/UpTheMightyReds &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9luk47/tifu_by_having_sex_too_soon_after_a_circumcision/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9luk47/tifu_by_having_sex_too_soon_after_a_circumcision/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9luk47</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9luk47/tifu_by_having_sex_too_soon_after_a_circumcision/" /><updated>2018-10-06T08:56:45+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by having sex too soon after a circumcision</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Anthios3l4</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Anthios3l4</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obligatory did not happen today, twas last (school) year&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At my school, there&amp;#39;s a student council, with a &amp;quot;president&amp;quot; (who&amp;#39;s better than the u.s. president), a vice president, and a few more. I was the design guy who wrote important documents, like announcements and fliers. They then go to my assistant, who is (supposed to) check the fliers, and then send them out. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The week was the first big assignment, I had to write an instruction manual for the science fair project submissions. It was simple, typing up a bunch of predetermined instructions, and formatting them. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seeing as I did not want to mess up, I came up with a cunning plan to insure my assistant did his job. This is where I fucked up. I slipped an instruction in, for setting up the project:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;All project assembly must be done in the nude.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then I gave it to my assistant to &amp;quot;check&amp;quot;. He didn&amp;#39;t check it. I was tired at the time, writting a 3-page essay for Language Arts, and forgot to check on the status of my manual. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5 days later:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I get called down to the principal&amp;#39;s office. He had a printed copy of the instructions I made. &amp;quot;What do you have to say for yourself, young man!?&amp;quot; He immediately said as I sat down. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can imagine how that went. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The verdict: I get suspended for 5 days. Me and my assistant get fired. All subsequent written documents get checked by a teacher. My dad thinks it was hilarious. At least, it was May on my last year at that school. Never saw that principal or my ex-assistant again. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL:DR: slipped a stupid instruction into a document, assistant didn&amp;#39;t check said document, got suspended for 5 days.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Anthios3l4&quot;&gt; /u/Anthios3l4 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9ly3qa/tifu_by_adding_stupid_instructions_to_a_manual/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9ly3qa/tifu_by_adding_stupid_instructions_to_a_manual/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9ly3qa</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9ly3qa/tifu_by_adding_stupid_instructions_to_a_manual/" /><updated>2018-10-06T18:14:14+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by adding stupid instructions to a manual.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Officerdaleday</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Officerdaleday</uri></author><category term="tifu" label="r/tifu"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sooo me and my buddies do this thing pretty frequently where we go to my shed where I have a pool table. We drink, listen to music, and play pool. Well usually we will play pool for a couple of hours then go out to the fire pit and light us a fire to end the night. It was like any other night I got the gas can poured some on the wood then threw a lit stick into the fire pit that had gas in it. All was well until the fire died down and I decided to toss some more gas on it as to reignite the flame (I do this every time I know it’s not smart) well needless to say the fire traveled up the stream and started burning the nozzle so I threw the gas can because I didn’t want it to explode in my hand. Well it was on the ground surrounded by fire underneath my grandparents favorite tree I didn’t want it to explode and catch the tree of fire so for some reason I kicked it. As I kicked it the gas got onto my leg and ignited thus burning for about 10 seconds or so. I had no idea how to get it to go out but I guess all of those years of people in elementary school cramming stop drop and roll into my head clicked so I got o the ground and started rolling around frantically. After we got it all to go out we drove me to the ER where they told me I had 2nd degree burns and I’m lucky that’s all I have. So let this be a lesson to all of you. Don’t use gas to start a fire. It won’t end well. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR I kicked a burning gas can and burned my leg extremely bad. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Officerdaleday&quot;&gt; /u/Officerdaleday &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m045h/tifu_by_lighting_a_fire_with_gasoline/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m045h/tifu_by_lighting_a_fire_with_gasoline/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_9m045h</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/9m045h/tifu_by_lighting_a_fire_with_gasoline/" /><updated>2018-10-06T22:18:04+00:00</updated><title>TIFU by lighting a fire with gasoline.</title></entry></feed>